Archibald M. Crossley Papers 1999.0007
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series VIII: Personal papers, undated, 1930-2002
  - Subseries D: Publications and publicity, undated, 1930-2002
    - Articles by Archibald M. Crossley, undated, 1930-1977; [3 folders] (Box 30)
      Subjects include: interview by Richard Baxter, and Public Opinion Quarterly "Polling in 1968" with Helen M. Crossley.
    - Articles about Archibald M. Crossley, undated, 1930-1997 (Box 30)
    - Awards, undated, 1930-1970 (Box 31, 32)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 30)
    - General, undated, 1944-2002; [3 folders] (Box 30)
      Articles and clippings.
    - Magazine portfolios and stereographic file use materials, undated (Box 33, 34)
    - Artifacts, undated; [5 items] (Box 35)
      Includes: Radio recorder, stereo viewer, and Crossley SD, Inc. badge.